

Elvis Wesley Vásquez Valarezo

Engineering in Electronics and Networks (Student) / Developer

Address: Los Olivos, Quito, Ecuador

Age: 26 yo

Telephone / cell: 0995988138 E-mail: elvis.vasquez@udla.edu.ec Github: https://github.com/wes9319

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elvis-vasquez/

Personal Web: https://wes9319.github.io



For a complete and interactive experience, visit my website: https://wes9319.github.io Professional extract: My knowledge is oriented to technological areas mainly software, electronics and networks. I have held various positions as a developer (web, mobile), designer, community manager, project manager, network administrator, IT support, among others. My greatest strengths are proactivity, availability, commitment to my work, ability to work under pressure and management of common and technical English.



EXPERIENCE





Developer – IT PEAP – IT Projects Analyst

Yanbal 2019 - Present

Functions: Development of projects associated to the IT area in the sub area of distribution and operations (ASP.net, WCF, SQL, SCRUM, html, css, js, iis, SSIS, Azure). Technical Support for the area, security patchs, multidisciplinary projects for the company.

Web Developer – Proyect Leader

Magnaflor *2018-2019*

Functions: Full stack development (LAMP stack), Develop new custom functionalities (js, html, css, php) on the current platform, Development of new platform (Vue js), Web and Server management, Data analysis, Performance optimization.

Developer – Designer

Spae 2014 - 2017

Functions: SPAE - Development of the tailored institutional website, design of physical and digital advertising banners, community management (facebook, twitter, google +, instagram), design and administration of the internal network, IT support, teaching, assistance and development of multidisciplinary projects.

Freelance - Development of independent start-ups (Market to Home, Healthy Pet), brand design, community management (Facebook, Intagram), development of multidisciplinary projects (calculation, programming, statistics, electronics), web development on request, video editing and photography.

See More...



EDUCATION •





Udacity

Front-end web developer nanodegree 2015

Universidad de las Américas

Engineering in Electronics and Networks 2015 - present



SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE



- ▶ Software development
- Networks(LAN, WAN)
- ▶ Analog and Digital **Electronics**
- Digital Marketing
- Multimedia Design
- Database Administration
- Networking
- Leadership
- Integrity

LANGUAGES AND SOFTWARE



Spanish (Native Language)

Advanced English)

Programming languages (C #, C, C ++, Java, swift, python, html, css, javascript, sql)

Operating systems (Windows, Linux, OSX)

Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver)

IDEs (Xcode, Visual Studio, Netbeans, Eclipse, SqlDeveloper, Arduino, Android Studio, etc.)

See more...